helpwithpcs.com 2015-04-27

# Privacy policy - Helpwithpcs.com

**What this privacy policy covers**   
This privacy policy covers the treatment of personal identifiable information that HelpwithPCs.com collects when you are on the HelpwithPCs.com website. 

**Collection and use of information**   
HelpwithPCs.com collects personally identifiable information when you use any of our online forms to request information or to make comments/suggestions. When you use these forms we ask for your name, email address and company information, once you have given us this information you are NOT anonymous to us. HelpwithPCs.com also automatically records information from your browser including your IP (Internet Protocol) address, the page you requested and browser information, this information is stored on our server and may be used to calculate the amount of visitors from different countries and to make your visit more enjoyable. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

**Cookies**   
Don't know what a cookie is? click here. 

HelpwithPCs.com utilises cookies when you sign up/login to our forum (currently offline) or when you use our contact forms. 

Some of the advertisements we have within our webpages require your browser to request the advert from the ad network website (just like your browser requesting a webpage), these companies can store their own cookies on your machine, other companies' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policy not this one. 

**Information sharing and disclosure**   
HelpwithPCs.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party whatsoever. 

**Jurisdiction**   
In using this website the parties agree to submit all disputes arising under this agreement to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales. 

**HelpwithPCs.com may make changes to this policy from time to time, if there are any substantial changes in the way HelpwithPCs.com use your personal identifiable information we will notify you by putting an announcement on our homepage.**
